Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Round one, match six of the Royal Knight Selection Exam.
Steel creation magic, full metal fortress!
Lightning magic, thunderbolt destruction!
Gotcha!
Weight magic!
Angel flapping ought to do the trick!
Go for it!
Oh boy, this is a lot of fun!
More!
Let's fight some more!
Thanks to their fine teamwork and Luck's unexpected increase in strength, Team K won their match.
Then, in the eighth and final match of round one...
It's gonna be Yuno and Noelle on a team together!
Can we please not do this?
The Silver House is divided. Noelle versus Solid.
Meanwhile, the bad blood between Alecdora and Yuno, born of a festering jealousy over Vongence's respect for the commoner, erupts into a full-blown grudge match between the two.
I will be the one to bring Sir Vongence's dream into reality!
Wind magic!
Towering tornado!
Why would I care about someone else's dream?
I only fight...
For my own dream.
Sea Dragon's Roar!
Crystal destroyed! Team P wins!
I'm not weak!
Not anymore!
Not any sign in.
ibly
Not idea in the world.
He's when he wants me.
Remember,
With his hands,
Too ниbe
Trouble…
We'll be right back.
This can't be.
There's no way.
Yuno managed to defeat my best spell.
He made it look like nothing.
He didn't even use his spirit magic.
All that power and he was still
halting back.
I will make Sir Vangeance's dream come true.
Here's the thing about you nobles.
When you stumble, you break.
Yeah!
That was an awesome fight, Yuno!
Same to you, Shortstack.
Now you're calling me that!
That was super cool, Yuno!
I could watch you fight like that all day long!
Here, I brought your usual post-battle dessert!
It would help me keep up my stamina.
Thank you for this.
It's just what I needed.
It's delicious.
Hey, Charmy!
You feeling okay?
Oh, come on, Spinehead!
Get over yourself!
That meant nothing!
Shut up, or I will step your nose
and struggle so you suffocate!
You hear me?
Take that!
I guess you're good.
Hey there.
So listen, just wanted to say you were great.
Honestly, I had no idea you were that powerful.
I feel like your personality changes quite a bit
when you're not doing the mushroom thing.
But still.
I've been listening to Solid since before the battle began.
The way that monster treats his baby sister is unacceptable.
Noel, an older brother's most important job
is to look after his siblings who are younger and weaker.
But judging by the many hurtful things I've heard him say,
it doesn't sound like he's even trying to uphold that responsibility.
So thrash him once and for all!
Um, thank you...
for what you said back there.
You did great work.
You know, that's a bit patronizing.
I am still royalty.
Let's do our best next time, too.
That monoskin training I did really helped me to regulate my magic.
I just have to keep this up,
and I'll be chosen as a royal knight!
Whew!
Those matches were really something else.
I can't wait for the next ones.
Yes, I require more amusement.
It's a shame that the two commoders who embarrass me
are still in the running.
Why won't they just lose?
All right, then.
Let's move on to the second round.
Oh, but before we start...
Go ahead.
You know what to do.
Sir!
Whoa!
The field!
It's shifting right in front of us!
So cool!
For us to get a good sense of your abilities,
we need to see you fight in various circumstances.
Hey, I'm back!
Hello there.
Take a good look.
This is the stage on which round two will be fought.
They can change the stage all they like,
but my beauty shall remain constant.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, as for this bit of human waste,
I'll wipe you away like the unsightly stain you are.
You'll find out I'm stickier than you think!
Talk trash all you want,
but Asta's strong and he has me with him.
So you're the one who's about to get wiped away, brother.
Hey, Asta!
You better not pull any punches with me.
Not a chance, Magna!
I'm kicking your butt!
I hope he doesn't break your ugly purple glasses.
Shut your freakishly big face, lady.
Oh my.
It looks like we're up against royalty.
I guess we'll just have to keep relying on that teamwork, huh?
You're laughing now,
but you looked worried when the field shifted.
So be honest.
You rigged the field with traps again this round, didn't you?
That's weird.
How'd he know?
I guess he must have picked up on some key or something.
All right, yeah, I did.
I came out here yesterday
and scattered a bunch of traps around the stage.
My intel told me this was where the test would be,
so I took advantage of that knowledge.
His intel?
But the location of the Royal Knight's exam
should be highly classified information.
What could his source be?
You placed the traps yesterday?
That's playing dirty, you stupid jerk!
It's part of the game, you idiot.
What?
Haven't you heard of information warfare?
Did you see something in the rules
saying not to set traps the day before?
Huh?
No one's yelled at me about it except you.
Hey, dude, stop!
Stop!
He won that argument fast!
Come on, let go!
Lost is so cute when he's mad!
Okay, then at least let us know where the traps are
so we can coordinate with you!
We'll work together!
Not happening.
You'd probably give it away to the enemy by accident.
I mean, he's not wrong.
Look, I've got my way of fighting
and I'm sticking to it.
Man!
Fine!
But if you're doing this your way,
then you'd better believe that I'm gonna do the same!
It looks like they're having a bit of an argument.
I hope it isn't anything serious.
They say that constant pickering is the truest sign of friendship.
I hope we'll have an argument ourselves someday.
Do you expect me to believe you'll come up with your own plan
with that puny little brain of yours?
No way.
Hey, I've got more brains than I know what to do with!
That's right!
You tell him, Asta!
The only small thing about you is your stature!
Yeah, so...
Hold on, what?
Your attention!
Team B!
Xerx, Mimosa, and Asta!
Versus Team C!
Kirsch, Sol, and Magna!
Round two, match one, begin!
Mimosa, you've stood by these peasants for too long,
allowing their crude mana to taint your own.
What a sad sight.
But fear not, sweet sister,
I'll release you from the grasp of these filthy beasts
before any of you can fight.
Cherry Blossom Magic!
Raging Magic Cherry Blossom Storm of Petals!
Plus my beautiful illusion!
Well now, that's quite a view.
So pretty!
This goes for a celebratory snack!
And for you!
Now, in the embrace of my most beautiful spell,
you're free to relinquish your soiled past self!
I know I topped big a minute ago,
but as hard as I've been training
and as much as I've improved,
I don't think I have a single spell that can counter this.
We shouldn't be hasty to act.
Our best bet is to sit tight and wait for them to set off a trap.
What an amazing spell!
I can't see a thing right now.
This might be our only way out.
What is he doing?
All right.
Here we go.
Feels like something big's about to happen.
That's the way.
Just like that.
Flow right on through me.
Darkness.
Come on.
Give me more.
What is that aura?
It doesn't feel like magic at all.
It's so strong.
So fierce.
It almost feels sinister.
Get ready!
Black Hurricane!
Whoa.
The cherry blossoms.
Wait.
Forget those.
He'll destroy my traps.
Wow.
Us looks good.
That attack.
It's from before.
It's the wiping out the fury blossoms bit by bit.
Impossible.
How'd that lowborn runt summon such a dreadful power?
Look at that.
He's pretty strong.
I know that wasn't easy.
Wow.
That was amazing!
Nice work!
Do you have any idea what you've just done?
You seem kind of pissed.
I guess you really do care about these fights.
Now, let's join forces and win this thing together!
You rotten imbecile.
What is this ugliness?
What in the world happened?
How did that commoner dispel all that magic?
Asta will only get stronger from here on.
And same goes for me.
Very impressive.
It would seem Asta's mastered yet another curious power.
Open wide gate!
Do you ever think before you act runt,
all the time I spent setting traps is wasted effort now?
It sure was.
They're all gone.
Rough, I know.
But it happened.
Time for you to give us a backup plan!
One where all three of us can win this!
Huh?
You're a crafty guy.
I'm sure you can think of something.
Come up with a new underhanded plan and we'll beat those guys fair and square!
You do realize that you're contradicting yourself, right?
Thank goodness.
Looks like the old Asta's back.
We don't need a plan.
That attack of yours should be more than enough to take out their team.
So go get them.
Totally would, but unfortunately for you,
that move takes a lot out of me,
so I'm gonna have to wait a while before I can whip it out again.
Why are you acting so damn happy about it?
Seriously, are you sick in the head, kid?
Don't you get it yet?
I want us all to fight as a freaking team!
So I don't care if you laid out all those traps yesterday.
It's time you started treating me and Mimosa like real partners!
We're fighting to get picked as royal knights.
If we win, it'll be on us to take down the eye of the midnight sun.
No one can fight them alone.
Not me, not you, not anyone.
There's only one way to beat a team as strong as that,
and guess what?
It's by making a team that's stronger!
Look, son.
Yes, my fellow magic knights are amazing people,
but the thing that makes us amazing
is that we never have to stand alone.
We all trust that if we face death, we'll face it together.
Look, the team we're up against right now
has the vice-captain of the Coral Peacocks in it.
He's a real piece of work, but he's also strong.
We need to hit that jerk hard and fast with everything we've got!
What the?
Hey, if you don't like my ideas, then just say so next time!
I want to join that royal guard like I want a pet tapeworm.
But my goals aren't about to achieve themselves,
so I guess that leaves me with no choice but to put you to use, you little punk.
I don't really care what your motive is.
All that matters to me is that we fight together.
As I'm sure you've noticed,
my magic attribute is ash,
and my specialty is trap magic.
But it's not exactly easy to create large-scale traps
like the ones from our last match.
Bigger traps require a lot more time and magic power to get going,
but they're also far more effective.
I told you I didn't get any sleep last night.
Wait, that was actually true?
You and your weird sword blew away a whole night of work just like that.
Yeah, sorry about that,
but we didn't really have a whole lot of options.
Let me think.
There are some traps that I can pull off right now.
Three, actually.
Okay, what are they?
First one's a snare trap.
Touch the magic circle, and it roots you in place,
then snares you.
Cool, cool. Go on.
Next up is the pitfall trap.
It's pretty straightforward, too.
You dig a hole and wait for your target to fall inside.
Very nice.
Trap type number three is the landmine.
It triggers a simple attack spell on contact.
Yeah, I remember that one.
All of those traps will disappear once they've been set off.
So unless I invest a lot of time and magic power in them,
we can't expect much payoff.
Now, what'll it be, kid?
Dear me, I can't believe it.
To think that my perfectly beautiful spell was corrupted and destroyed by that peasant's insidious weapon.
You know, I can't say I'm surprised.
See, I knew that Aust had been practicing that move plenty.
The kid put in the work, and now he's got an ace up his sleeve.
Maybe this will teach you not to underestimate commoners.
Oh, side note, I'm one myself.
Don't say it!
You mean to tell me you're a commoner, too?
Yeah, and if it mattered, you would have noticed.
Oh, no!
I could never fight beside a commoner.
I would just end up being defiled.
Hey, wait up, you damn narcissist!
We already fought together once!
What's it gonna hurt to do it one more time?
There's no need.
I have power enough to eliminate these fools by myself.
You two stay there and protect the crystal.
You know what?
Fine.
Do whatever you want.
But if you think I won't do the same, guess again.
Good grief.
The male animal certainly is stupid.
There's no doubt about that.
Commoners are brutish.
They are unclean, and they are fundamentally lacking in magic power.
How shameful.
He shouldn't even be allowed to share a stage with royalty,
let alone to stand at our beautiful sides.
There's Mimosa.
Probably heading for our crystal.
And I'm sensing that Zerk's fellow's magic power from right there.
As for the human waste, I'm getting nothing from him.
What in the world is he, and where?
Hey, you want some crystal?
Come and get it!
There you are, you filthy urchin.
Cherry blossom magic!
Dance of the beautiful cherry blossom blades!
These petals slipped through the smallest openings.
You're really strong!
Such ugly cowardice.
You shans escaped me!
Come kick my butt!
Should be easy for a royal!
It may be faint, but I still sense magic.
This is an obvious attempt to entrap me.
I can see through this plan with ease, you craven wretch.
Cherry blossom magic!
My beautiful clones!
Run out of the traps!
Did you really think you could stop me with such a shoddy plan?
First, you chose to enter a cramped space which constrains your blade,
and then you gave up your only escape route.
I didn't think of that!
If only I was his smartest royalty!
Be gone!
Commoner!
Now, how could this be?
My clones disposed of every trap spell in the area.
I was sure of it.
True.
You've got a real good nose for magic,
and you rely on it way too much, dumbass.
See, we knew you'd be on the lookout for trap spells,
so we dug this pit with plain old elbow grease.
Who's dirty now, royal?
They made this not with magic, but with effort and muscle.
I should have expected this.
You pathetic primitives.
Still, I'll fly right out!
I really hate to do this to Mimosa's big brother,
but I'm gonna have to knock you out for a bit.
Stay away from me, you filthy beast!
I told you that you and me could make a good team.
Well, for the record, I was only using you.
It's so stupid, at least!
Well, now it's given the time.
minimum don't trust your ener過usions.
You can check your hand at night!
I'll see you in the minute so you don't trust your date.
Number two weeks here,
you will continue your dreams.
Take care.
Thank you.
Never happy with the looks of his potential brides, he remained forever alone.
In time, his warped personality drove everyone who could have loved him away.
His twilight years were remarkably lonely.
Ah, there's a sight for sore eyes.
Oh, so pretty.
You truly are beautiful.
If I could just touch.
And so my stupid brother met his miserable end.
At least I was in beautiful company.
If you don't stop fawning over your own face, I might just drown you myself.
Friends, don't be ridiculous.
I'm just using these people to reach my own goals, that's all.
Black Clover, page 79.
Mr. Delinquent versus Muscle Brains.
My magic is trapping the unaware.